God, you're beautiful.
天啊，你真美
Why are we fighting this?
我們為什麼要抗拒這種感覺呢？
You know you want it to happen as much as I do.
你跟我一樣都想要的
I want you. I need you.
我想要你，我需要你
Let me make love to you.
讓我跟你做愛
I don't wanna stand in the way of true love or anything..
我不想要介入這場真愛還是什麼的
but I think a cantaloupe might hurt less.
但是我想如果你找一個甜瓜來愛 可能會比較不痛
No, I'm rehearsing my lines.
不是啦，我是在練習我的台詞
They're giving me a romantic story on Days of Our Lives.
他們在《我們的日子》裡頭幫我 安插了愛情故事情節
It's the first time my character's gotten one. I'm nervous. I want it to be good.
這是我的角色第一次戀愛 我很緊張，我想要把他演好
I haven't seen you this worked-up since you did that dog-food commercial..
自從你上次做那個狗食廣告之後 我就沒有看你這麼認真練習過
and you thought you were gonna be with a real talking dog.
而且那次你還以為是要跟 一隻真的會說話的狗一起演出
Yeah, that was a disappointment.
是啊，那次我真的很失望
You wanna come down to the set and tell me if I'm doing okay?
你想過來片廠看我表現如何嗎？
- Are you serious? - Yeah.
-真的嗎？ -是啊
You just have to promise not to get thrown out again.
只要你保證不要再被趕出去
- That was an honest mistake. - Right.
-那只是個錯誤 -沒錯
"Oh, my God. Is this the men's room? I feel so foolish.
「天啊，這是男廁所嗎？ 我真是好蠢」
Have you always known you wanted to be an actor?"
「你一直都很清楚自己要當演員嗎？」
Yeah, that was an awesome day.
是啊，真是精采的一天
The One With Rachels Dream
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
- Hey. - Hey.
-嘿 -嘿
You guys wanna come eat dinner at the restaurant in the next few weeks?
你們接下來幾個星期 有想要到我們餐廳用餐嗎？
- I'd love to. - Well, you can't.
-我很想 -喔，可能沒辦法
- We're booked solid for the next month. - Well, I can't give you a massage..
-我們下個月全部都被訂滿了 -喔，我不能幫你按摩
because my license has been revoked again.
因為我的執照又被取消了
- Phoebe, what happened? - Well, it was an accident, you know.
-菲比，發生什麼事？ -喔，只是個意外
It's a lot of oil and sometimes the hand just slips.
當用很多精油的時候 有時候手是會滑的
So the restaurant's doing well, you say?
所以你是說餐廳生意很不錯囉？
It is so great. There are people lining up in the street..
好極了，還有人排隊排到街上…
to taste my food. Saturday, there's a waiting list of 50 people.
只是為了嘗嘗我做的食物 下個星期六的後補名單上有五十個人
I know how that feels. Last semester, I had two students..
我知道那是什麼感覺
who wanted to take my 1:00 class, but it was full.
上個學期我有兩個學生想上我的 一點鐘的課，但是那堂課已經滿了
So they had to take my 5:00.
所以他們只能上我五點的課
That's not the same.
那一點也不像
Have I got a surprise for you. Pack your bags.
我要給你個驚喜，回家去打包吧
Oh, no. You guys aren't supposed to get divorced for seven years.
喔，不，你們七年之內不可以離婚的
What? No, I'm taking Monica to a romantic inn in Vermont.
什麼？不，我是要帶摩妮卡 去佛蒙特州的浪漫小木屋度假
Oh, good. Okay, good for you. Trying to recapture the magic.
還好，好的，很好 試著找回往日情懷
- So can you get out of work? - Honey, I can't.
-你可以請假嗎？ -親愛的，我沒有辦法
- Things are crazy at the restaurant. - You're really that busy?
-餐廳現在忙瘋了 -你真的那麼忙嗎？
Yeah. I'm sorry, I really am.
是的，我很抱歉，我真的很忙
That's okay. I'll just try and reschedule.
沒關係，我來試著更改日期好了
Hi, this is Chandler Bing. I made a reservation there..
嗨，我是錢德賓 我有預定過小木屋
and I need to change it.
現在我需要更改日期
What do you mean, it's nonrefundable? Well, can I just come some other time?
無法退費是什麼意思？ 我不能擇期再去嗎？
Can't you make an exception?
你不能破例嗎？
Tell them I'm a chef at a big New York restaurant.
告訴他們我是紐約一家大餐廳的主廚
Tell them that in two weeks, I will once again be a masseuse in good standing.
告訴他們在兩星期以後 我又會再度成為很棒的按摩師
Look, this is ridiculous. I'm not paying for that room, okay?
聽著，這實在太可笑了 這錢我不會付的，你聽懂了嗎？
Well, thank you very much.
好的，非常謝謝你
Yeah, I'm going to Vermont.
我得去佛蒙特州
- Don't worry, use your travel insurance. - I don't have travel insurance.
-別擔心，你可以用你的旅遊保險 -我沒有旅遊保險
Well, this is what happens when people live on the edge.
當人們活在危機邊緣的時候 就是會發生這種事
- Honey, what are you gonna do? - I'll go.
-親愛的，你該怎麼辦呢？ -我去就是了
Okay, I'll pick you up at 10.
好的，我十點去接你
Oh, go with you?
喔，跟你去嗎？
Oh, I can't go.
喔，我不能去
Why don't you take Ross?
你何不跟羅斯一起去呢？
Don't you think that'll be a little weird? I mean, two guys in a romantic inn?
你不覺得那會有點奇怪嗎？ 兩個大男人住一間浪漫小木屋？
- No, not if the room has two beds. - I guess.
-不會啊，如果有兩張床就好了 -我猜也是
It still seems a little.. "Moonlight boat ride"?!
但是還是有點… 「月光船游」！
（銀杯攝影棚）
Joey, is this the bed where Olivia lost her virginity?
喬伊，這是奧莉維亞獻出第一夜 的那張床嗎？
I don't know, but one of the extras sure did.
我不知道，倒是有個臨時演員獻出過
Listen, Rach. Thanks again for coming down to watch my scenes.
瑞秋，再次謝謝你過來看我的演出
Please, honey. Just the fact that you want me here to support you, I'm..
拜託，親愛的 我光是想到你要我的支持，我就…
Oh, my God. Is that Christian Saunders? He is so gorgeous!
喔，天啊，那是克利斯桑德嗎？ 他真的是非常帥！
And also, so gay.
而且是非常同志
Well, in my head, he's done some pretty not-gay stuff.
在我腦海中，他做了很多不是同志的事
Well, at the Christmas party, him and Santa did some definitely-gay stuff.
在聖誕晚會上，他跟聖誕老公公 做了很多絕對是同志的事
Joey? Joey, we're ready for you.
喬伊？喬伊，我們準備好要拍你了
Okay. All right, wish me luck.
好的，祝我好運
Okay. Not that you need it, but good.. God! Is that Chase Lassiter?
你不是真的需要運氣才做的好，但… 天啊！那是傑斯萊西特嗎？
- He's straight, right? - Rach, if you weren't here wondering..
-他是異性戀，對吧？ -瑞秋，如果沒有你在這裡猜測…
if these guys were gay, I don't know if I could do this.
這些男的是不是同志… 我還真的不知道我能不能演的好
I'm sorry, you're right. I'm sorry. Good luck.
我很抱歉，你說的對 很抱歉，祝你好運
On a bell, please. Quietly.
拜託準備好，安靜
And action!
開拍！
Drake, what are you doing here?
德克，你在這裡做什麼呢？
Stopping you from marrying the wrong man..
阻止你嫁給不對的人…
and making the biggest mistake of your life.
犯下你這輩子最大的錯誤
- Get out. - You don't love him.
-出去 -你並不愛他
What do you know about love?
你知道什麼是愛嗎？
I know what I felt that night when we kissed under the bridge.
我知道那晚我們在 橋下接吻的感覺是什麼
- That kiss never happened. - Well, what about this one?
-那個吻並沒有發生 -那麼，這個呢？
Now, I told you to get out.
我說過了，滾出去
Fine, I'll go.
好，我走
But let me ask you one question.
但是讓我問你一個問題
- You look real familiar. Have we..? - Shh! He's asking her a question.
-你看起來很面熟，我們有…？ -噓！他要問她問題
Can you live the rest of your life never knowing what we could have been?
你可以渡過一生而不知道 我們如果在一起會是如何嗎？
- I don't have a choice. - Yes, you do.
-我沒有選擇 -你有選擇的
Yes, you do. I'm the one who doesn't have a choice because I..
你有的，我才是那個沒有選擇的人 因為我…
Because I can't stop loving you.
因為我無法停止愛你
- Don't say that. - Tell me to stop.
-別那樣說 -你叫我停下來吧
Just..
你只要…
tell me to stop.
叫我停下來
- Cut! - No!
-卡！ -不！
Or, cut. You know, that's your call.
卡也好，那是你的決定
- Everything was delicious. - Thank you.
-每道菜都很美味 -謝謝你
It was. The duck in particular was superb.
真的，尤其是鴨肉更是美味絕倫
Thank you.
謝謝你
You haven't said anything.
你還沒有開口說話
Actually, I do have one small complaint.
其實我有一個小小的抱怨
Well, please, I welcome criticism.
喔，請說，我歡迎各種批評指教
The musician right outside the restaurant is kind of a mood killer.
餐廳外面的歌手有點破壞氣氛
What musician?
什麼歌手？
What are you doing here?
你在這裡做什麼呢？
You said you had customers lined up in the street, so I'm here to entertain.
你說你們的客人都排隊排到街上 所以我就過來娛樂他們了
- Great. - Yeah, it really has been great too.
-很好 -是啊，一切都進行的很好
They must have seen me play before..
他們一定有看我表演過
because they requested a bunch of my songs.
因為他們一直要點我的許多歌曲
Yeah, "You Suck"..
像是《你遜斃了》
and "Shut Up and Go Home."
還有《閉嘴回家去》
Listen, Phoebe. You know how much I love listening to your music..
聽著，菲比，你知道我很愛聽你的歌的
- but.. - But what?
-但是… -但是什麼？
This is kind of a classy place.
這是個蠻高級的場所
Okay, say no more.
好的，不用多說了
Everyone!
大家一起來！
Classy, huh?
高級，不是嗎？
Hi, Chandler Bing. I have a reservation.
嗨，我是錢德賓，我有訂房
Welcome to the Chestnut lnn. Where are you joining us from?
歡迎來到小木屋 你們是從哪裡來的呢？
- New York. - The Big Apple.
-紐約 -大蘋果
He's wound up. We had to stop at every maple-candy stand on the way here.
他太興奮了，我們來這裡的路上 每間楓糖糖果店都有停下來
I ate all my gifts for everybody.
我吃光了要買給大家的禮物
I'm sorry, there's no record of your reservation in the computer.
我很抱歉，電腦沒有登記您的預定
- That's impossible. Check again, please. - Check again, please.
-那是不可能的，請再查一次 -請再查一次
- I'm sorry, it's not here. - It's not there.
-我很抱歉，沒有 -沒有
Let me get this straight. I called to try to cancel my reservation..
讓我搞清楚，我有打過電話來 試著要取消我的預約
was told it's not refundable. Then we drove six hours all the way up here..
你們告訴我不能取消 然後我們開了六小時的車到這裡
- and now we don't have a reservation? - I don't know what to say.
-現在你又說我們沒有訂房？ -我不知道該說什麼
She doesn't know what to say.
她不知道該說什麼
Just give us the cheapest room you have.
那給我們最便宜的房間就好了
The only thing we have available is our deluxe suite. The rate is $600.
我們現在剩下來的房間就只有精緻套房 價格是每晚六百元
- That's insane. - It's totally insane.
-這真的過分 -真是太過分了
Dude, let's drive home. We'll hit all the maple-candy stores on the way back..
我們開車回家吧，可以在回家路上的 再去每間楓糖糖果店
and if they're closed, then maybe we'll tap a tree and make some ourselves.
而且如果他們關門了 或許我們可以找棵樹自己做楓糖
Does that room have a closet I can lock him in?
那個房間有個衣櫥 可以讓我把他鎖起來嗎？
- We'll take it. - Great.
-我們要那間房 -太好了
They are totally ripping us off! Three hundred dollars each?
他們完全就是在剝削我們 一人三百塊？
"Each?" I'm your date.
「一人」？我是你的約會伴侶耶
So I pay for everything and have no sex.
所以我得負擔所有的開銷 而且還不能炒飯
Oh, life before Monica.
喔，在有摩妮卡之前的生活就是如此
Dude, don't worry about it.
老兄，別擔心
I know how to make your money back. This is a nice hotel. Plenty of amenities.
我知道要如何讓你花的錢回本 這是間不錯的飯店，有很多福利設施
We just load up on those. Like those apples. Instead of taking one..
我們只要盡量拿走那些東西就好了 像是這些蘋果，不要只拿一個
I take six.
我給他拿六個
Great. At $100 an apple, we're there.
太棒了，一個蘋果一百塊，我們辦到了
Come on, you get the idea. You know, we'll make our money back in no time.
別這樣，你知道我的意思的 我們很快就可以回本了
- Dude, you're shaking. - It's the sugar. Could you hold the apple?
-老兄，你在發抖耶 -是糖在搞怪，可以幫我拿蘋果嗎？
- Hi. - Hey.
-嗨 -嘿
Joey, I gotta tell you, I have been thinking all day about that scene you did.
喬伊，我要跟你說 我整天都在想你的演出
I mean, you were amazing.
你真是棒透了
You know, the writing was good. And the director's good.
你知道的，編劇很棒 導演也很棒
And my costar's good.
我的對戲演員也很棒
But they're not as good as me!
但是他們還是不如我棒！
You have to tell me what happens tomorrow.
你得告訴我明天會發生什麼事
I'm going over the script now. Wanna read lines with me?
我現在正在看劇本 你要幫我一起對台詞嗎？
Me? Oh, I'm not an actress.
我嗎？喔，我不是演員的料
- All right, I can ask Monica. - Screw her! That part is mine!
-好吧，我去找摩妮卡 -去她的！那角色是我的！
Okay, so just from the top of the page right here.
好的，從這一頁開頭開始
Okay.
好的
Hello, Drake. I'm surprised to see you here.
哈囉，德克，我很訝異會在此看到你
- I can't believe you married him. - Well, what choice did I have?
-我不敢相信你嫁給他了 -我能有什麼選擇呢？
He was keeping my sister in a dungeon.
他把我妹妹關在地牢裡
So, what about us? Everything we feel for each other?
那我們呢？我們對彼此的感覺呢？
It's over. You have to accept that.
結束了，你必須要接受
How can I, knowing I'll never hold you in my arms again..
當我知道我再也無法把你擁入懷中 或是碰觸你的肌膚
or touch your skin or feel your lips..
或是感覺你的雙唇 或是永遠無法跟你做愛
knowing I'll never make love to you?
我怎麼能夠做的到呢？
How can I accept that I can never kiss you again..
我怎麼能接受 我再也無法親吻你
when it's all I can do not to kiss you right now?
而我現在最想要做的 就只是親吻你
Kiss me.
親我
What?
什麼？
Kiss me.
親我
- Rach, it doesn't say that. - No, I'm saying it.
-瑞秋，劇本不是那樣寫的 -不，是我說的
- But.. - Just don't talk.
-但是… -不要說話
Well, that's new.
那倒是新的夢
Hi, this is Ross Geller in suite 206.
嗨，我是206號房的羅斯蓋勒
I've forgotten a couple of things.
我忘了帶幾樣東西
Could you have some complimentary toiletries sent up to my room?
你可以幫我送幾樣贈送的 衛生用品到我房間裡來嗎？
Thank you. Okay, a toothbrush, toothpaste..
謝謝你 好的，牙刷、牙膏
razor, mouthwash, deodorant, floss, Band-Aids, shaving cream, after-shave.
刮鬍刀、漱口水、體香劑、牙線 繃帶、刮鬍乳液、收斂水
And I feel like I'm forgetting something.
我覺得我好像漏了什麼東西
Is there anything else you have that I haven't asked for already?
你還有什麼東西是我沒有提到的呢？
Yeah, go ahead, send up some tampons.
好，那就送一些衛生棉條上來
- What'd you get? - USA Today.
-你拿了什麼？ -《美國時報》
Nice. Put it with the others.
很好，跟其它的放在一起
And I also got two more apples.
而且我還多拿了兩個蘋果
We're four short of a bushel!
還差四個就可以做水果花籃了！
God, I feel so alive. I love being in the country!
天啊，我覺得充滿活力 我喜歡鄉間生活！
Also, got these great salt and pepper shakers..
還有，我從餐廳裡拿了這些…
- from the restaurant. - That's not cool.
-鹽巴胡椒罐 -這不好
Dude, none of this is cool.
兄弟，這一切都不好
Look, Chandler, you have to find the line between stealing..
聽著，錢德，你要找出介於偷竊跟…
and taking what the hotel owes you.
拿取飯店欠你的東西之間的界線
For example: A hair dryer, no, no.
例如，吹風機，不不不
But shampoos and conditioners, yes, yes.
但是洗髮精跟潤發乳，可以可以
Now, the salt shaker is off limits.
鹽巴罐是不行的
But the salt..
但是鹽巴…
I wish I'd thought this through.
我希望我剛剛有想清楚點
I think I get what you mean, though. Like, the lamp is the hotel's..
我想我知道你的意思了 就像檯燈是飯店的…
but the bulbs.. Oh, you already got that.
但是燈泡… 喔，你已經拿了
Not my first time in a hotel, my friend.
我的朋友 這可不是我第一次住飯店
- Okay, how about this? - No, no, no.
-好的，那這個呢？ -不不不
- You can't take the remote control. - Yes, but the batteries.
-你不能拿遙控器 -是的，但是可以拿電池
Thank you. Thank you very much.
謝謝，太謝謝你了
- Let's celebrate with some maple candy. - No!
-我們來吃楓糖慶祝吧 -不！
At least tell me where you hid it.
至少告訴我你把它藏哪裡去了
（中央咖啡廳）
- Can I ask you a question? - Yeah.
-我可以問你一個問題嗎？ -好的
Have you ever had any..
你有沒有作過任何…
weird, romantic dreams?
奇異的… 浪漫的夢呢？
Let me think.
讓我想想
When I was younger, I used to dream that I got married to Mayor McCheese.
當我較年輕的時候 我曾經夢過跟麥當勞的卡通市長結婚
And on our wedding night, I ate his head.
然後在我們新婚之夜，我吃了他的頭
Okay.
好的
Well, this is like that..
這一點也…
in no way.
不像是那樣
I had a dream last night that I wanted to kiss Joey.
我昨晚夢到我想要親喬伊
Wow! You mean like "kiss him" kiss him?
哇！你是說真的親吻他嗎？
Oh, yeah. I mean, it was pretty intense.
是啊，我是說那種很激情的
- What brought that on? - I don't know.
-為什麼會那樣呢？ -我不知道
Maybe it had to do with the fact I saw him do a love scene.
或許跟我看到他演出那場愛情戲有關
- A love scene? With who? - Olivia.
-愛情戲？跟誰呢？ -奧莉維亞
Olivia?! I thought she was marrying Connor?!
奧莉維亞？我以為她要跟康納結婚了
Oh, right. Real life more important.
對了，現實生活比較重要
- You think my dream means anything? - I don't know.
-你認為我的夢代表什麼嗎？ -我不知道
I mean, you saw him do a love scene.
你看到他演出愛情戲
So maybe you don't have a thing for Joey. Maybe you have a thing for Drake.
或許對喬伊沒有感覺 或許你是對德克有感覺
Well, it was Joey reading Drake's lines in the dream.
是啊，在夢裡是當喬伊 在念德克台詞的時候
Of course it was. Trust me, when it comes to psychology..
當然囉，相信我，只要是跟心理學有關
I know what I'm talking about.
我是很內行的
I took two psych classes in college.
我在大學的時候修過兩堂心理學
You took the same class twice.
你一堂課重修兩次
- It was hard! - I know.
-那很難耶！ -我知道
- Hey. - Hi, Phoebe.
-嘿 -嗨，菲比
Here, Monica, look what I got to wear when I play at your restaurant.
摩妮卡，瞧瞧我為了要到你餐廳演唱 買了什麼
Wait.
等等
Right? I think this might even class up "The Ballad of the Uncircumcised Man."
我想這會提高 「沒有割包皮男人之民謠」的格調
Phoebe..
菲比…
maybe I wasn't clear before.
或許我之前說的不夠清楚
I really love listening to your music here.
我真的很喜歡在這裡聽你的音樂
But my restaurant, it's sort of an upscale place.
但是我的餐廳是比較高級的地方
Right, yeah, okay. I'll ask the butler to fetch my diamonds out of the vault.
好的，好吧，我會要管家幫我把 我的鑽石從保險箱拿出來
Phoebe, it's not what you wear.
菲比，不是你穿的衣服的關係
It's sort of your songs.
是你的歌
I just don't think you should play at the restaurant anymore.
我只是覺得你不應該再到餐廳演唱了
Okay. Fine, I'll just..
好的，沒關係，我就…
I'll take the hat back.
我把帽子拿回去退
There.
好了
Hey, so, you guys, the funniest thing happened at work the..
嘿，我辦公室發生一件最好笑…
My songs aren't good enough for your restaurant?
我的歌不夠格登上你們餐廳的大堂嗎？
Okay, we're still on that.
好吧，我們還在談那個
- I didn't say they weren't good enough. - Then what's wrong with them?
-我沒有說它們不夠格 -那有什麼不對呢？
What, they don't go with your tiny portions of pretentious food?
是怎樣？他們不夠格配你的 一丁點份的，自負的食物嗎？
- Tiny portions? - Yeah, well, "Excuse me.
-一丁點份？ -是啊不好意思…
I ordered the smoked salmon appetizer, but I can't see it. I can't see it."
我點了熏鮭魚 但是我看不到鮭魚，我看不到
- Phoebe, it's not about quantity. - Well, it's not about quality.
-菲比，份量不是最重要的 -喔，品質也不是最重要的
Oh, really? You wanna talk about quality?
真的嗎？你想要談品質嗎？
Have you ever heard of a "key"? It's what some people sing in.
你有聽過什麼叫「調」嗎？ 那是大家唱歌要對的
Well, at least all my songs don't taste like garlic.
至少我所有的歌都沒有蒜頭味
Yeah, there are other ingredients, Monica.
是的，摩妮卡 還有其它的東西可以拿來調味的
So that's what we're doing.
所以我們要這樣做囉
When I'm in a coffeehouse bopping along to one of your songs..
當我在咖啡廳裡跟著你的歌打拍子時
I'm wearing earplugs.
我是有戴耳塞的
Earplugs or cloves of garlic?
是耳塞還是蒜頭塞呢？
You know what? I take back what I said before.
你知道嗎？我收回我所說的話
Keep playing at the restaurant, because with your music driving people inside..
繼續到餐廳演唱吧 因為你的音樂會把人逼進餐廳裡…
my bar sales have gone up like crazy.
我們吧檯的營業量會瘋狂激長的
What are people having, the garlic martini?
他們都點什麼呢？蒜頭馬丁尼嗎？
So you wanna hear my work story?
那你想要聽聽我今天工作的事嗎？
I'll save it.
我省省好了
Here's your bill. We hope you enjoyed your stay.
這是您的帳單，希望您還住的愉快
Oh, we did. And you still have all your lamps.
喔，我們很愉快 而且你們的檯燈都還在
- I didn't factor in the room tax. - Dude, don't worry about it.
-我沒有算進稅金 -兄弟，不用擔心
I found an unattended maid's cart. We're way ahead of the game.
我找到了一台沒人看管的女傭拖車 我們是居領先地位的
- Oh, my God. - What?
-喔，我的天 -怎樣？
There's something new in the bowl.
那盆子裡有新的東西
- Look, we have enough. Just walk away. - No, but I want the pine cones.
-聽著，我們拿夠了，走吧 -不，但是我想要松果
- There's a forest right outside. - It's not the same.
-外面就有一片森林 -那不一樣
- No, look. She's gonna see us. - No, she won't. I'm sly.
-不，她會看到的 -不，她不會，我會動作很快的
Okay, go quick.
好吧，快點
Thank you for a delightful stay.
謝謝你們令人愉快的服務
My maple candy!
我的楓糖糖果！
It's just you. I thought someone was swinging a bag of cats against the wall.
原來是你，我還以為有人 拿了一袋子的貓往牆上揮
You'd better get back in that kitchen. The garlic's not gonna overuse itself.
你最好回去廚房 蒜頭是不會自己多用自己的
- Okay, you have to stop playing now. - Why?
-好了，你現在必須要停唱了 -為什麼？
The only person my playing is bothering is you.
我的歌干擾到的人只有你
- Oh, yeah? Let's settle this. Come on. - Get your garlic peelers off me.
-是嗎？我們來解決這件事，來吧 -把你的蒜頭手拿開
Excuse me? Excuse me?
不好意思，不好意思
Hi, I'm Monica Geller. I'm the head chef here.
我是摩妮卡蓋勒，這裡的主廚
Okay, I was actually expecting a little applause there, but whatever.
好的，我本來真的希望有人鼓掌的 但是沒關係
Quick question. By a show of hands..
一個問題，請大家舉手回答
how many of you were bothered by this woman's singing outside?
你們有誰被這女人 在外面唱歌干擾到呢？
Okay, okay. Well, I have a question.
好的，好的，我有個問題
You can put your hand down.
你們現在可以把手放下了
You made your point earlier when you spit in my guitar case.
你剛剛吐口水到我的吉他箱上 就已經表達的很清楚了
Okay, okay. How many of you enjoyed the music outside?
好的，你們有誰喜歡外面的音樂呢？
Let me ask you this question. How many thought the music was fine..
讓我問你們這個問題 有誰認為音樂還好…
but not in keeping with the tone of the restaurant?
但是跟本餐廳的格調不符呢？
Okay, well, who identified this restaurant's tone as "pretentious-comma-garlicky"?
好的，誰認為這個餐廳的格調是 「自以為是又充滿蒜頭味」呢？
Okay, who thinks the food is delicious and a little pretension never hurt anyone?
好的，有誰覺得食物是很美味的 而一點點做作是沒關係的？
Okay, well, all right, who thinks the food is fine, the music was fine..
好了，沒關係，有誰覺得食物很好 音樂也很棒
but your evening was ruined by this incessant poll-taking?
但是你的晚餐已經被這個持續不斷 的民意調查給毀了？
Excuse us.
不好意思
All right, here's a question.
好了，我問你
Who was so worried about her restaurant being fancy..
有誰認為她的餐廳是那麼的高級…
that she made a big deal about her friend playing her music..
讓她過分的擔心 她的朋友會演唱不適當的音樂…
and feels really bad about it now?
而現在真的覺得很難過呢？
Well, who was so stupid and stubborn..
有誰很愚蠢又很頑固…
that she lashed out against her friend's cooking..
批評了她朋友的烹飪技術…
which she actually thinks is pretty great?
而其實她是覺得她的烹飪很好呢？
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry too.
-我很抱歉 -我也很抱歉
Hey, you wanna stick around and I'll whip you up some dinner?
嘿，你要不要留下來 然後我幫你準備晚餐呢？
Yeah, as long as it's free.
好啊，只要是免費的
The food here is ridiculously overpr..
這裡的食物真的是超貴…
Who hopes the hand-raising thing is still cute enough that you won't hate me?
誰希望舉手這件事 還可愛到使你不要恨我呢？
- Hey. - Hey.
-嘿 -嘿
Joey, do you have peanut butter on the back of your head?
喬伊，你的頭後面有花生醬嗎？
Oh, man. I thought I got it all.
喔，天啊，我以為我都擦掉了
How..?
怎麼會…
How?
怎麼弄到的呢？
I was making a peanut butter smoothie, right?
我正在做花生醬冰沙
I couldn't find this little plastic thingy that goes in the top of the blender.
我找不到果汁機上面那個小塑膠蓋
And I thought, "Well, you know, how important can that be?" Right?
然後我想 「那個小東西有什麼重要的呢？」
Turns out, very.
結果是非常重要
Wow, definitely just Drake.
哇，一定只是因為德克
- What? - How's it going with Drake?
-什麼？ -德克演的如何呢？
- I don't think it's going very well. - What?
-我想可能演的不是很好 -什麼？
That scene I saw was so good.
我看的那一場戲很好啊
Well, I'm feeling really insecure about the one we're shooting tomorrow.
我對明天要拍的那場戲 覺得很沒安全感
Is this that thing you do when you say you're bad so I'll give you a compliment?
你是不是又故意說自己很糟 然後讓我來讚美你呢？
A little.
有點
No, I really am worried. I have to make it convincing that I'm in love with Olivia.
不，我是真的很擔心 我必須要演得像是我真的愛上奧莉維亞
- So? - So I've never played that.
-所以呢？ -所以…我從來沒有演過那種戲
Oh, honey, it can't be that hard. I mean, you've been in love before.
喔，親愛的，那不會很難的 你也有談過戀愛啊
Well, just once..
嗯，只有一次…
with you.
就是跟你
Okay. Well, this could be a little awkward.
好了，這實在是有點尷尬
I'm just gonna blow past it.
我們跳過好了
Well, look, can't you just use that method-actor thing..
聽著，你何不運用你那個特殊方法
where you use your real-life memories to help you in your performance?
就是利用你的真實生活回憶 來幫助演出呢？
What the hell are you talking about?
你在說什麼？
All right, look, just try to remember how you felt when you were in love..
好的，只要試著回憶起 你在談戀愛時候的感覺
and think about that when you're playing the scene.
然後在演出的時候回想起那些感覺
Okay. Yeah, I think I can do that.
好的，是啊，我想我做的到
Yeah. Okay, there's this party scene coming up.
好的，有個晚會的劇情
And Olivia and her husband are there..
奧莉維亞跟她老公就在那裡
and all Drake wants to do is grab her and kiss her, but he can't.
而德克想要做的只有抓住她 然後親吻她，但是他不能
That makes me think about those times I wanted to grab you and kiss you..
那讓我想起許多時候我好想抓住你 然後親吻你
but you didn't know, so I would just pretend everything was cool..
但是你並不知道 所以我只能假裝沒事
but really it was killing me.
但這真的讓我很受折磨
Joey, you never talked about that before.
喬伊，你從來沒有說過這些
Hey, you know what else I could use?
嘿，你知道我還可以用什麼嗎？
There's this scene where Drake sneaks into Olivia's bedroom..
有一場戲是德克偷偷溜進 奧莉維亞的房間
and she doesn't know he's there, which never happened with us.
她不知道他就在那裡 當然，我們之間沒有發生過這樣的事
I mean, he knows he shouldn't be there, but he just wants to look at her.
他知道他不應該去那裡 但是他只想看看她
You know?
你知道嗎？
And I remember all those mornings before you even put on your makeup..
而且我記得有好幾個早上 就在你開始要化妝之前
when I would think to myself, "My God, she is beautiful."
我會想「天啊，她真是美麗」
And it hurt so much because I knew I could never tell you.
而且讓我好心痛 因為我知道我永遠不能告訴你
But it was worth it just to be there looking at you.
但是光是看著你 我就覺得心滿意足了
Thanks, dude. This is great!
謝了，真是太棒了！
I got you something from Vermont.
我從佛蒙特州幫你帶了些東西
Besides tampons and salt?
衛生麵條跟鹽巴以外的東西嗎？
Oh, my God.
喔，我的天
Maple candy. That's so sweet of you.
楓糖糖果，你真是貼心
That's weird, it's empty.
真是奇怪，裡面是空的
Hi, you guys. What's going on? You guys wanna hang out or..?
嘿，你們好，怎麼了呢？ 你們要一起怎樣嗎？
Do you guys hear a buzzing?
你們有聽到嗡嗡聲嗎？